badi.com 2019-12-06

# Privacy Policy | Badi Blog

Update to our privacy policy:

As part of our ongoing effort to improve transparency and guarantee that the personal information you give us is processed legally, we have updated our Privacy Policy.

******1 Introduction**

This Privacy Policy (the “ **Policy** ”) describes how BADIAPP 2015, INC. SUCURSAL EN ESPAÑA (“ **BADI** ” or “ **we/us** ”) collects, uses, stores, shares and protects the personal information derived from the use made by the user (the “ **User** ”) both of the platform accessible via the domain [https://badi.com/es/](https://badi.com/es/) (the “ **Website** ”) and our Application (the “ **App** ”), and through the services that are specifically offered to you via the Website or the App (referred to indistinctly as the “ **Services** ”). 

If you do not agree with the Policy, you can consult us at [info@badi.com](mailto:info@badi.com)

******2 Who is the data controller of your personal data?**

The personal data you provide in the User registration process, along with any data submitted during the provision of the services or that BADI may obtain through the Website and/or the App, will be processed by BADI, domiciled at Avenida Meridiana 89, 08026, Barcelona (Spain), and contact email address [info@badi.com](mailto:info@badi.com). 

This Policy governs the processing of personal data. All the terms used in the Policy will have the meaning established in the Terms and Conditions of Use (which can be viewed at this [link](https://badi.com/blog/en/general-conditions-use/)) unless they are expressly defined in this Privacy Policy.

******3 For what purpose do we process your data?**

The personal data will be collected and processed in the context of the Services offered through the Website and/or the App for the following purposes: 

(a) To manage User registration and to be able to control the development and compliance with the contractual relationship with you, in accordance with the Terms and Conditions of Use. In particular, BADI will process the following categories of data for the purposes that are specified below: 

(b) To respond to queries that may be submitted by Users in connection with the App and the Website or the Services

Furthermore, and only with the consent of the User in each case, we will use their data for the following additional purposes: 

(a) To better know their preferences through evaluation of their profile, using the data to improve the use of the Website and/or the App, prevent fraud and improve the service.

(b) If so requested, to send the User advertising or commercial information, including by electronic means, about BADI’s products and services that may be of interest to them.

(c) To process their participation in competitions and specific promotions. 

In addition, the User’s personal data will be processed when BADI has to fulfill a legal obligation under tax and anti-money laundering laws.

******4 What is the legitimate interest for processing the data?**

The legal basis for processing the data is the performance of the Terms of Use of the Services, where the data processing is strictly necessary to be able to use the Website and the App and, therefore, to allow Users to benefit from the services made available to them. 

With respect to additional purposes, these are legitimized by the consent given by the User, which may be revoked at any time without affecting the provision of the Services. Specifically, Users may withdraw their consent at any time by contacting us at [info@badi](mailto:info@badi.com).

With regard to compliance with the obligations imposed on BADI, the legal basis is established by applicable law (including Spanish Law 58/2003, of December 17, General Tax Act and Spanish Law 35/2006, of November 28, on Personal Income Tax and partial modification of the Corporate Income Tax Act, Nonresident Income Tax Act, and Wealth Tax, and their respective implementing regulations, and any other applicable legislation).

******5 How long will we keep your personal data?**

BADI will keep the personal data of Users while they remain registered customers or users of the Website and/or the App, and the personal data will be retained after the termination of the contractual relationship, duly blocked, for the time necessary to answer for any liabilities that may be derived from the relationship. 

In particular, the Personal Data required for responding to queries made and delivering electronic marketing communications will be processed for as long as the User does not revoke the consent given and, once that consent has been withdrawn, for the time necessary to answer for any liabilities that may have arisen. In any case, when the personal data is not required for the purpose for which it was obtained and until it is not finally canceled, it will be retained in a blocked form.

******6 Who will your data be sent to?**

BADI may communicate the personal data of Users when so required by law, for defending its legitimate rights and interests, or when necessary in accordance with the services contracted by Users. They may also be accessed by third party service providers and computer and technical support services, some of which are detailed below.

Certain systems, data and services are hosted on Amazon Web Services (“AWS”), with its servers located in Frankfurt (Germany) and in the Google Cloud Platform. Your data may be transferred internationally to that company’s servers in the United States. This international transfer of personal data is covered by the EU-US Privacy Shield agreement and, therefore, provides adequate guarantees for the protection for your personal data. More information is available at the following link:  [https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active). 

To conclude, we inform you that BAD relies on other companies to provide certain services related to the Website and/or the App, like billing or payment of Services through our platform. More information on each company is available at the following links: 

  * Mixpanel: [https://mixpanel.com/legal/privacy-policy/](https://mixpanel.com/legal/privacy-policy/)
  * Adjust: [https://www.adjust.com/privacy-policy/](https://www.adjust.com/privacy-policy/)
  * Google Analytics:  [https://policies.google.com/privacy/update](https://policies.google.com/privacy/update)
  * Firebase: [https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy/](https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy/)
  * Sendgrid: [https://sendgrid.com/policies/privacy/](https://sendgrid.com/policies/privacy/)
  * Nexmo: [https://www.nexmo.com/privacy-policy](https://www.nexmo.com/privacy-policy)
  * Stripe: [https://stripe.com/privacy](https://stripe.com/privacy)
  * HotJar: [https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy](https://www.hotjar.com/legal/policies/privacy)
  * Intercom: [https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy](https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy)
  * Aircall: [https://aircall.io/privacy/](https://aircall.io/privacy/)
  * Zendesk:[https://www.zendesk.com/company/customers-partners/privacy-policy/](https://www.zendesk.com/company/customers-partners/privacy-policy/)
  * Transcom: [https://www.transcom.com/en/data-protection-notice-cookie-policy](https://www.transcom.com/en/data-protection-notice-cookie-policy)
  * Nestpick: [https://www.nestpick.com/privacy-policy/](https://www.nestpick.com/privacy-policy/)

******7 What are your rights as the data subject?**

******8 Information updating**

The User may update the information held by BADI through the settings available in their account, or by writing to [info@badi.com](mailto:info@badi.com). We remind you that in order for BADI to adequately provide the Services, the User must keep their information up to date, and accordingly, agrees to regularly check the information provided to ensure it is accurate.

You can ask us to stop sending you marketing emails or communications at any time. To this end, you can change the communications preferences in the settings section of your account, or contact us at [info@badi.com](mailto:info@badi.com). However, this will not prevent us from sending emails and other communications related to the Services, since these are necessary to comply with the contractual relationship between us and the User.
